stopzilla.com 2012-05-11

# Privacy Policy - Security Software by STOPzilla

## IS3, INC. (STOPzilla)

### http://www2.stopzilla.com

Effective Date: 04th of October 2010   
Last Edited: 18th of November 2011 

* * *

### General Information

IS3, INC. (STOPzilla) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following information to learn more about our privacy practices. 

  * This policy covers what personally identifiable information IS3, INC. (STOPzilla) collects and how it is treated. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify visitors to the http://www2.stopzilla.com Web Site. This information may be limited to an IP address or extend to personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number. 
  * This policy only applies to http://www2.stopzilla.com and does not extend to the practices of other Web Sites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

* * *

### Contact Information

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this privacy policy. 

Our Internet address is located at [http://www2.stopzilla.com](http://www2.stopzilla.com/)

> **IS3, INC. (STOPzilla) IS3, INC. (STOPzilla)  
>  2200 NW 2nd Ave,   
>  Suite 201   
>  Boca Raton, FL 33431   
>  FL USA **
> 
> You may contact us by e-mail at [privacy@stopzilla.com](mailto:privacy@stopzilla.com)   
>  You may contact us by phone on 561-807-6058 Ext: 220 or 877-877-9944 Ext: 128 

* * *

### Dispute Resolution

IS3, INC. (STOPzilla) is committed to resolving any dispute you may have regarding our privacy policy quickly and efficiently. 

Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative. Our customer service will promptly correct any errors. 

* * *

### Browser Settings

During the installation process, STOPzilla presents an opt-out "Home Page Protection" dialog. The default option protects your current home page from being hijacked by an unauthorized process. Although this option can be turned off from within the STOPzilla setup, we highly recommend that you keep this option in-force at all times to prevent malware from taking over your browser. 

* * *

### Information Collection

When visiting Web Sites certain information about you and your computer can sometimes be collected. This section explains what information IS3, INC. (STOPzilla) collects, and how it is used. 

> ### Information Collected
> 
> \- What information do we collect and why? 
> 
> We collect the following identifiable information about our visitors: 
> 
>   * user.name _(optional)_
>   * user.home-info.online.email _(optional)_
>   * user.home-info.telecom.telephone _(optional)_
>   * user.business-info.telecom.telephone _(optional)_
>   * user.business-info.online.email _(optional)_
>   * dynamic.clickstream 
>   * dynamic.http 
>   * dynamic.searchtext 
>   * dynamic.cookies 
>   * dynamic.miscdata 
> 
  
>  We collect identifiable information for the following reasons: 
> 
>   * Web Site and System Administration 
>   * Research and Development 
> 
  
>  Collecting information about your computer will allow us to potentially diagnose and repair computer related problems. 
> 
> Our Web Site generates server log files automatically. These log files are used to generate statistical information and error reports to ensure the Web Site runs with a minimum of disruption. They are not actively used to identify individual visitors. 
> 
> The STOPzilla product may collect anonymous usage metrics using a service called DeskMetrics. DeskMetrics is a real-time analytics module that has been integrated into STOPzilla. The information gathered is collected and aggregated by deskmetrics.com and is used to improve our product. For more information about Deskmetrics and what information may be collected please refer to the [DeskMetrics Analytics Privacy Policy](http://deskmetrics.com/analytics/privacy-policy/). You may opt out of this service at installation. 
> 
> ### Information Recipients
> 
> \- Who has access to the information collected?   
> 
> 
>   * Ourselves and/or our entities acting as our agents or entities for which we are acting as an agent. 
> 
  
> 
> 
> ### Information Retention
> 
> \- How long is this information retained? 
> 
>   * We do not have a retention policy for this area of the Web Site. 
>
